sathyabamauniversity.ac.in 2018-12-10

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Sathyabama Institute of Science and Technology website and reviewing our privacy policy.

We respect the privacy of those who visit our web site. In accordance with this, we have created this policy in order to demonstrate our privacy commitment to our users

We collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party. If you want to know more about how we record non-personal information about your visit or how we use information that you voluntarily submit, read on

**Non-personal Information We Record**

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, our website's operating system will automatically record some general information about your visit.

During your visit, our web operating system will record:

| 

The **type of Operating System** that you use (such as Windows, Unix, or Mac).  
  
---|---  

| 

The **type of Browser** (such as "Netscape version X" or "Internet Explorer version X") that you are using.  

| 

The **Date and Time** you visit our site, and the **web pages that you visit** on our site.  

  *  

| 

The **Internet Domain** for your Internet service, such as "xyz.com" or "xyz.net" if you use a private Internet access account or "yourcollege.edu" if you connect from a college or university domain.  
  
We use this information for statistical analysis, to help us make our site more useful to visitors. This tracking system does not record information about individuals.
